Finding Aid for Stephen M. Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) records, 1916-2017
Bentley Historical Library
- Russell A. Stevenson and Predecessors Series, 1916-1960
  - Supplemental Administrative Records, 1924-1960
    - Programs for Full-Time Students and Faculty, 1924-1960
      - Academic Advisors, Committee, 1945 (Box 20)
      - Academic and Admissions Committee, 1950-1960; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Admission Requirements, Committee, 1941 (Box 20)
      - Business Research, Bureau
        - General, 1929-1959; 5 folders (Box 20)
        - Memos, 1949-1952; 5 folders (Box 20)
        - Projects and Programs, 1951-1953; 3 folders (Box 20)
        - Projects and Programs, 1958-1960; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Cheating Problems, Committee, 1948 (Box 20)
      - Courses
        - Accounting, 1940-1955 (Box 20)
        - Actuarial Science, 1941-1955 (Box 20)
        - Advertising, 257 and 258, 1934 (Box 20)
        - Bank Management and Investments, undated (Box 20)
        - Business Economics, Proposed, undated (Box 20)
        - Business History, 1953 (Box 20)
        - Commercial and Trade Association, 1948-1952 (Box 20)
        - Corrective English, 1939-1941 (Box 20)
        - Cost Accounting, undated (Box 20)
        - Financial Principles, undated (Box 20)
        - Foreign Trade, 1936-1940 (Box 20)
        - Grand Rapids Courses, 1946-1950; 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Industrial Relations, 1935-1940 (Box 20)
        - Insurance Courses, 1949-1951 (Box 20)
        - Institutional Management, 1939-1940 (Box 20)
        - Internal Revenue Service, Advanced Training Center, 1954-1957; 4 folders (Box 21)
        - Marketing, 1938 (Box 21)
        - Programs of Study, 1941 (Box 21)
        - Purchasing, 1942 (Box 21)
        - Real Estate, 1935-1956; 6 folders (Box 21)
        - Real Estate, 1935-1956; 4 folders (Box 21)
        - Report Writing, 1942 (Box 21)
        - Retailing, 1944-1950; 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Secretarial Courses, 1942 (Box 21)
        - Small Business Program, 1948-1951; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Special Program for Women, 1942-1943 (Box 21)
        - Suggested Courses
          - Air Transportation, 1946-1954 (Box 21)
          - International Business, 1957 (Box 21)
          - Productivity, 1950-1951 (Box 21)
          - Public Relations, 1949-1958; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Trust Function, 1933-1934 (Box 21)
      - Conference Center, Committee, 1958 (Box 22)
      - Counseling Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 22)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1942-1961; 5 folders (Box 22)
      - Defense Training, Committee, 1941 (Box 22)
      - Discrimination, Committee to End, 1949-1951 (Box 22)
      - Economics Faculty, Committee on Joint Research Projects, 1950 (Box 22)
      - Executive Committee, 1942-1960 (Box 22)
      - Extension Courses
        - Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 22)
        - Planning Your Financial Future, 1953-1957 (Box 22)
        - Real Estate, 1954-1958; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Faculty Personnel Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Research Funds, 1932-1939 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Social Committee, 1950-1959 (Box 22)
      - Freshmen Admission Committee, 1952 (Box 22)
      - Grading System, Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 22)
      - Graduate Committee, 1946-1960; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Honorary Degrees, Committee, 1929-1960; 5 folders (Box 22)
      - Hospital Administration, 1947-1959; 8 folders (Box 22)
      - Industrial Relations, Bureau, 1935-1960; 6 folders (Box 23)
      - Library, 1924-1959; 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Ph.D Examination Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 23)
      - Placement Committee, 1947-1959 (Box 23)
      - Placement Office, 1955-1960 (Box 23)
      - Reorganization of Dean's Office, 1958 (Box 23)
      - Research Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 23)
      - Scholarship Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 23)
      - Secretarial and Clerical Staff, 1950-1956 (Box 23)
      - Secretarial Practices, Committee on, 1943-1959 (Box 23)
      - Sorting and Tabulating Committee, 1948 (Box 23)
      - Student Conduct, Committee, 1937-1938; 1946-1948; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Student Expenses, Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 23)
      - Trade Association Executives Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 23)
      - Weekly Broadcast, Committee, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Programs for Special Groups, 1932-1960
      - 1932-1941
        - Accounting, 1932-1933; 1935; 1937-1939 (Box 23)
        - Bankers, 1938-1941 (Box 23)
        - Consumer Credit, 1937-1940 (Box 23)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 23)
      - 1945-1946
        - General (Box 23)
        - Radio Broadcasts (Box 23)
      - 1946-1947
        - General (Box 23)
        - Real Estate Appraisal (Box 23)
      - 1947-1948
        - General (Box 23)
        - Accounting Employers (Box 23)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 23)
        - Retailing Dinner (Box 23)
      - 1948-1949
        - General (Box 24)
        - Accounting Employers (Box 24)
        - Bureaus of Business Research (Box 24)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 24)
        - Small Business Conference (Box 24)
      - 1949-1950
        - General (Box 24)
        - Accounting Employers (Box 24)
        - American Accounting Association (Box 24)
        - American Statistical Association (Box 24)
        - Annual Reports Forum, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Convocation Celebrating SBA's 25th Anniversary (Box 24)
        - Federal Tax Lecture Series (Box 24)
        - Michigan Accounting Conference (Box 24)
        - Michigan Retail Clothiers and Furnishers Association (Box 24)
        - Profit Sharing (Box 24)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 24)
        - Sales Refresher Course (Box 24)
        - Statistical Quality Control (Box 24)
      - 1950-1951
        - General (Box 24)
        - Annual Reports Forum (Box 24)
        - Cost Accounting for Furniture Manufacturers (Box 24)
        - Michigan Bank Study Conference (Box 24)
        - Public Utilities Executives (Box 24)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 24)
        - Small Business (Box 24)
        - Statistical Quality Control (Box 24)
      - 1951-1952
        - General (Box 24)
        - Bank Management Training (Box 24)
        - Blue Cross (Box 24)
        - Foreign Operations (Box 24)
        - Marketing Research (Box 24)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 24)
        - Public Utility Program (Box 24)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 24)
        - Real Estate Conference (Box 24)
      - 1952-1953
        - General (Box 24)
        - Actuarial Science, 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 24)
        - Alumni Conference (Box 24)
        - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 24)
        - Edison Electric Institute, 4 folders (Box 25)
        - Marketing Research (Box 25)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 25)
        - Public Utility Program (Box 25)
        - Sales Management (Box 25)
      - 1953-1954
        - General (Box 25)
        - Advertising (Box 25)
        - Alumni (Box 25)
        - Bank Training (Box 25)
        - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 25)
        - Executive Development Program (Box 25)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 25)
        - Public Relations (Box 25)
        - Public Utility (Box 25)
        - Sales Management (Box 25)
      - 1954-1955
        - General (Box 25)
        - Advertising (Box 25)
        - Alumni (Box 25)
        - Executive Development (Box 25)
        - Marketing Research (Box 25)
        - Michigan Consumer Finance Association (Box 25)
        - Mortgage Bankers Association of America (Box 25)
        - Public Utility Executive (Box 25)
        - Real Estate Clinic (Box 25)
      - 1955-1956
        - General (Box 25)
        - Advertising (Box 25)
        - Alumni (Box 25)
        - Banking, School of (Box 25)
        - Banking Study Conference (Box 25)
        - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 25)
        - Executive Development (Box 25)
        - Furniture Manufacturers Sale Conference (Box 25)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 25)
        - National Consumer Credit Conference (Box 25)
        - Public Utility Executive Program (Box 25)
        - Sales Management (Box 25)
      - 1956-1957
        - General (Box 26)
        - Advertising (Box 26)
        - Alumni, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - American Business Writers Association (Box 26)
        - American Gas and Electric Association (Box 26)
        - Bank Study Conference (Box 26)
        - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 26)
        - Michigan Business Executive Research
          - Council (Box 26)
          - Conference (Box 26)
        - Public Utility Executive Program (Box 26)
        - Sales Management (Box 26)
      - 1957-1958
        - General (Box 26)
        - Advertising (Box 26)
        - Alumni (Box 26)
        - Consumer Finance Management (Box 26)
        - Executive Development (Box 26)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 26)
        - Public Utility Executive Program (Box 26)
        - Student Council Award Lecture (Box 26)
      - 1958-1959
        - General (Box 26)
        - Advertising (Box 26)
        - Alumni (Box 26)
        - American Electric Power Program (Box 26)
        - Banking Study (Box 26)
        - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 26)
        - Business Administration Leadership Award (Box 26)
        - Business Law (Box 26)
        - Executive Development (Box 26)
        - Great Lakes Industrial Development Council (Box 26)
        - Hospital Administrators (Box 26)
        - Michigan Business Executives Research Conference (Box 26)
        - Public Utilities Executive Program (Box 26)
      - 1959-1960
        - General (Box 26)
        - Alumni (Box 26)
        - Business Administration Council Leadership Award (Box 26)
        - Ford Foundation-Research in Public Relations (Box 26)
        - International Business Conference (Box 26)
  - Relations with Other University Units, 1923-1960
    The Relations with other University Units series documents the school's dealings with other parts of the university. It has been divided into two subseries, Senior Administrators/Centralized Functions and Schools, Colleges, Departments and Similar Divisions.
    - Senior Administrators/Centralized Functions, 1923-1960
      The first sub-series, Senior Administrators/Centralized Functions, dates from 1923 to 1960 and includes records relating to university non-teaching units. Included is correspondence with the regents, the university's most important administrators, such as the president and vice-presidents, as well as communications with units such as the General Library and the Registrar's office. The records are arranged alphabetically, generally by title of office, but some filing irregularities exist. For example, correspondence with Vice-Presidents Briggs, Niehuss and Pierpont is filed under "v", while correspondence with Vice-President Smith is filed under "s".
      - Admissions Office, 1957 (Box 26)
      - Associate Dean of Faculties (William)
        - Instruction Costs Study, 1956-1958 (Box 26)
        - General, 1954-1960 (Box 26)
      - Buildings and Grounds, 1924-1940; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Business Office, 1947-1948 (Box 26)
      - Extension Service
        - Upper Peninsula, 1960 (Box 27)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 1923-1939 (Box 27)
          - 1942-1948 (Box 27)
        - Flint College, 1953-1959 (Box 27)
        - Foreign Students, Counselor to, 1924-1939 (Box 27)
        - Health Service, 1929-1938 (Box 27)
        - Library, General
          - 1943-1947 (Box 27)
          - 1950 (Box 27)
          - 1957-1958 (Box 27)
        - News Service, 1949-1950 (Box 27)
        - Personnel Office, 1950-, 1953-1959 (Box 27)
        - Plant Department, 1957-1958 (Box 27)
        - President's Office
          - 1926-1941 (Box 27)
          - 1942-1947 (Box 27)
          - 1949-1952 (Box 27)
          - 1958-1960 (Box 27)
        - Provost's Office
          - 1939-1942 (Box 27)
          - 1943-1948 (Box 27)
          - 1949-1951 (Box 27)
        - Regents, Board of
          - Actions of, circa 1924-1941 (Box 27)
          - Communications to, circa 1924-1941
            - 1942-1950 (Box 27)
            - 1954-1960 (Box 27)
        - Registrar's Office
          - 1923-1939 (Box 28)
          - 1942-1948 (Box 28)
          - 1948-1953 (Box 28)
        - Registration and Records, Office of, 1953-1958 (Box 28)
        - Smith, Shirley W. (Secretary and Vice-President), 1925-1942 (Box 28)
        - Staff Benefits Office, 1960 (Box 28)
        - Statewide Education-Dorr, 1958 (Box 28)
        - Student Affairs, Office of, 1947; 1950; 1956-1959 (Box 28)
        - Summer Session, Office of, circa 1951-1960 (Box 28)
        - University College, circa 1927-1929 (Box 28)
        - University Relations-Brandon, circa 1954-1956 (Box 28)
      - Vice-President
        - Briggs, circa 1949-1950 (Box 28)
        - Niehuss
          - circa 1949-1953 (Box 28)
          - Ca., 1954-1956 (Box 28)
        - Pierpont
          - Ca., 1951-1953 (Box 28)
          - Ca., 1954-1960 (Box 28)
        - Stirton, ca., 1956-1960 (Box 28)
      - Watkins, Herbert G., Secretary, ca., 1949-1954 (Box 28)
    - Schools, Colleges, Departments, and Similar Divisions, 1923-1960
      Schools, Colleges, Departments and Similar Divisions also date from 1923 to 1960. As the name implies, records found here largely deal with the various teaching units of the university. Filing is again alphabetical, generally by name of unit, but some subject headings, such as "Combined Curriculum" exist. Subject headings often include correspondence with units that also have an independent heading. For example, under "Combined Curriculum" a folder titled "Business and Law" is found while later in the file "Law School" is also found.
      - Air Science, Department, 1953 (Box 28)
      - Adult Education Division, 1958 (Box 28)
      - Alumni Relations, Bureau, 1932-1940 (Box 28)
      - Architecture and Design, College, 1939; 1949-1959; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Calendar Committee, 1949-1961 (Box 28)
      - College Relations Committee, 1950-1960; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Combined Curriculum
        - Business and Letters, 1923-1948 (Box 28)
        - Business, Letters and Law, 1930-1936 (Box 28)
        - Business and English, 1924-1940 (Box 28)
        - Business and Forestry, 1928 (Box 28)
        - Business and Law, 1939-1941 (Box 28)
      - Computer Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 28)
      - Development Council, 1952-1958; 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Economics Department, 1936-1951 (Box 29)
      - Education, School, 1936-1954 (Box 29)
      - Engineering, College, 1924-1958; 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Fees, Various Committees on, 1935-1959; 5 folders (Box 29)
      - Foreign Students, Admission Policy, 1945-1946 (Box 29)
      - Forestry and Conservation, School, 1929-1953 (Box 29)
      - Graduate School, 1942-1960; 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Higher Education, Center for the Study of, 1958-1960 (Box 29)
      - Housing Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 29)
      - Housing Research Committee, 1947 (Box 29)
      - Human Adjustment, Institute, 1947-1953 (Box 29)
      - Intermediate Staff Appointments, Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 29)
      - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute, 1957-1960; 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute, 1957-1960; 5 folders (Box 30)
      - Law School, 1929-1959 (Box 30)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College, 1924-1959; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Medical School, 1936-1953 (Box 30)
      - Michigan Alumni Fund, 1953-1956 (Box 30)
      - Michigan Daily, Dean's Subcommittee on, undated (Box 30)
      - Military Science Department, 1923-1932 (Box 30)
      - Moving Expenses of New Faculty, Committee, 1957 (Box 30)
      - Music, School, 1933; 1938 (Box 30)
      - Natural Resources, School, 1953-1954 (Box 30)
      - Office Personnel, Committee on, 1931-1947 (Box 30)
      - Outside Employment, Committee on, 1927-1934; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Parking, University Council Committee, 1941 (Box 30)
      - Pharmacy, College of, 1951-1953 (Box 30)
      - Program and Policy, Committee, 1934-1940 (Box 30)
      - Psychological Services, Bureau of, 1957 (Box 30)
      - Psychology, Department, 1946-1948 (Box 30)
      - Public Administration, Institute, 1945-1957; 7 folders (Box 30)
      - Public Administration, Institute, 1945-1957; 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Public and Social Administration, Institute, 1941 (Box 31)
      - Public Health, School, 1950-1952 (Box 31)
      - Public Relations, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
      - Publications, Committee, 1925-1940 (Box 31)
      - Regional Research, Institute, 1951-1953 (Box 31)
      - Registration and Records, Advisory Committee to Office of, 1954-1957 (Box 31)
      - Relations with Institutions of Higher Education, Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 31)
      - Research Club, 1926-1938 (Box 31)
      - Research, Committee of Law and Business, 1931-1932 (Box 31)
      - Senate Council, 1924-1940 (Box 31)
      - Social Research, Institute, 1946-1953; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Social Science Division, Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 31)
      - Social Science Research, Committee, 1932-1936 (Box 31)
      - Social Sciences, Committee, 1950-1958; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Statistical Research Laboratory, 1958-1959 (Box 31)
      - Statistics, Committee, 1945 (Box 31)
      - Student Relations, Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 31)
      - Television, Special Committee, 1952-1956 (Box 31)
      - Undergraduate Studies, Senate Committee, 1927 (Box 31)
      - University Affairs, Senate Advisory Committee, 1928; 1937-1939; 1954-1956; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - University Research, Bureau, 1928-1931 (Box 31)
      - Urban Planning Committee, 1958 (Box 31)
      - Willow Run, 1946-1955; 3 folders (Box 31)
  - Personal, 1926-1960
    The Personal series, dating from 1926 to 1960, contains the personal papers which Dean Stevenson left at the school. They are divided into two sub-series, General, and Lear, Inc. The General papers, 1926-60, are arranged alphabetically and contain a wide variety of information. There are records Stevenson brought from Minnesota, information regarding his negotiations to come to Michigan as dean, and an extensive run of "publications" that includes both printed material and speeches. Stevenson served on the board of various corporations, but the best documented is that of Lear, Inc. Stevenson's board records date from 1951 to 1960 and represent not only documents sent to him as a board member, but also his activity on committees dealing with special compensation to be paid both to the firm's most senior executives as well as to the general work force.
    - General, 1926-1960
      - A, 1935-1943 (Box 31)
      - American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1932-1944; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - B, 1936-1943 (Box 31)
      - Bell, James Ford, 1941-1942 (Box 31)
      - Bullis, Harry A., 1943 (Box 31)
      - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1942-1944 (Box 31)
      - C, 1937-1942 (Box 31)
      - Canadian-American Relations, 1939-1942 (Box 31)
      - Cincinnati, Curriculum Material (Box 31)
      - Committee Appointments, University of Minnesota, 1929-1944 (Box 31)
      - Conference on State University Schools of Business, 1944 (Box 31)
      - Contact Lists, University of Minnesota (Box 31)
      - Crofts, F.S., Publishers, 1941-1942 (Box 31)
      - D-E, 1926-1944 (Box 32)
      - F, 1932-1944 (Box 32)
      - Fillipetti, George, Forward to "Operating Results of Manufacturing Plants in Minnesota", undated (Box 32)
      - G, 1926-1943 (Box 32)
      - Gown in Town, undated (Box 32)
      - Griffin, Clare E. [includes 33 1/3 recording of speech, 1961], 1927-1943 (Box 32)
      - H, 1933-1943 (Box 32)
      - Hormel, Jay C., 1940-1943 (Box 32)
      - I, 1931-1938 (Box 32)
      - Insurance Inventory, 1937-1943 (Box 32)
      - J-K, 1930-1944 (Box 32)
      - L, 1933-1943 (Box 32)
      - Lear Stock, 1953-1960 (Box 32)
      - M, 1940-1943 (Box 32)
      - Manuel, R.W., 1937-1944 (Box 32)
      - Michigan Building Plans, 1943-1944 (Box 32)
      - Michigan Position (Dean of SBA), 1943; 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Minnesota, University of, 1943-1944; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - N, 1938-1943 (Box 32)
      - Newcomen Society, 1941 (Box 32)
      - Northern States Power Co., 1942-1943 (Box 32)
      - Northwestern National Bank, Director's Material, 1943-1944 (Box 32)
      - Notes (Box 32)
      - O-P, 1935-1938 (Box 32)
      - Paton, William A., 1926-1944 (Box 32)
      - Personal
        - Curriculum Vita, 1934-1943 (Box 32)
        - General, 1926-1943; 4 folders (Box 32)
        - Ph.D Thesis (Box 32)
        - Publications
          - Dean's Page (Box 32)
          - General, 1926-1942; 4 folders (Box 32)
          - General, 1943-1955; 48 folders (Box 33)
      - R-S, 1934-1944 (Box 33)
      - Smaller War Plants Corp., 1943-1944 (Box 33)
      - Stassen, Harold, 1941-1943 (Box 33)
      - T, 1927-1944 (Box 34)
      - Travel, 1942-1944 (Box 34)
      - W-Z, 1938-1943 (Box 34)
    - Lear, Inc., 1951-1960
      - Board of Directors Meetings
        - 1951-1956, 27 folders (Box 34)
        - 1957-1960, 21 folders (Box 35)
      - Compensation Committees (Bonus, Incentive, Stock Option, etc.), 1952-1960; 11 folders (Box 35)
      - Compensation Committees, 1952-1960; 6 folders (Box 36)
      - General
        - 1951-1952 (Box 36)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 37)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 38)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 39)
        - 1958-1960 (Box 40)
- Floyd A. Bond and Successors Series, 1926-1984; 1960-1979
  The Bond subgroup (48) is largely composed of records generated during Bond's years as dean, 1960-79, although a few items created by his successor, Gilbert Whitaker, and predecessors are also housed here, making the series full dates 1926-1984. The basic arrangement of the subgroup mirrors that of Dean Stevenson, as it contains series entitled Dean's Administrative Records, Supplemental Administrative Records, Relations with other University Units, and Personal; it also includes two additional series: Audio Materials and Publications.
  - Dean's Administrative, 1926-1983; 1960-1979
    Bond maintained a large Dean's Administrative file dating from 1926 to 1983 (primarily 1960-79) that is arranged alphabetically, generally by either personal name or subject heading. Included is information regarding accreditation of the school, affirmative action, alumni, annual reports (of the dean to the president), Bond's correspondence and memos, detailed budget information, Dearborn campus, enrollment, facilities, fundraising, publications, memos to and from assistants such as Associate Dean Robert Roberts, students, and a few files created by Gilbert Whitaker. Taken together, these files are perhaps the single most informative source of information regarding the school contained within the collection.
    - A General, 1960-1963 (Box 40)
    - Accreditation by American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 40)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 40)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 40)
    - Adams, Thomas T. (Associate Dean), 1962-1966 (Box 40)
    - Administrative Organization, 1968-1979 (Box 40)
    - Admissions
      - Directors, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
      - General, 1962-1968 (Box 40)
      - Policies, 1963-1970 (Box 40)
      - Procedures, 1972 (Box 40)
      - Visitation Program, 1971-1974 (Box 40)
    - Affirmative Action
      - Availability Assessments
        - 1971-1972 (Box 40)
        - 1973-1976 (Box 40)
        - 1976, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Black Enrollment
        - 1963-1970 (Box 41)
        - 1969-1971 (Box 41)
        - 1970-1982 (Box 41)
      - Bynoe, Patrick H., (Appeal), 1974-1975 (Box 41)
      - Cash, W.L., 1969 (Box 41)
      - Education of Negroes for Business, 1966-1976 (Box 41)
      - General
        - 1966-1971 (Box 41)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 41)